export const data = [
  {
    question: "Jamie Vardy was signed by Leicester from which non-league side?",
    option1: "ketting Town",
    option2: "Alfreton Town",
    option3: "Grimsby Town",
    option4: "Fleetwood Town",
    ans: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "What was the score in the Euro 2012 final?",
    option1: "2-0",
    option2: "3-0",
    option3: "4-0",
    option4: "5-0",
    ans: 3,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Who won the Man of the Match award in the 2014 World Cup final?",
    option1: "Mario Goetze",
    option2: "Sergio Aguero",
    option3: "Lionel Messi",
    option4: "Bastian Schweinsteiger",
    ans: 1,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Against which country did Wayne Rooney break the England goalscoring record?",
    option1: "Switzerland",
    option2: "San Marino",
    option3: "Lithuania",
    option4: "Slovenia",
    ans: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "Which team has won the African Cup of Nations a record 7 times?",
    option1: "Cameroon",
    option2: "Egypt",
    option3: "Senegal",
    option4: "Ghana",
    ans: 2,
  },

  {
    question:
      "You can find the oldest footballer in the world playing in which country?",
    option1: "Malaysia",
    option2: "Ecuador",
    option3: "Japan",
    option4: "South Africa",
    ans: 3,
  },

  {
    question:
      " Chelsea beat which team 8-0 to secure the 2009-10 Premier League title on the final day of the season?",
    option1: "Blackburn",
    option2: "Hull",
    option3: "Wigan",
    option4: "Norwich",
    ans: 3,
  },

  {
    question: " Which team did Porto beat in the 2004 Champions League final?",
    option1: "Bayern Munich",
    option2: "Deportivo La Coruna",
    option3: "Barcelona",
    option4: "Monaco",
    ans: 4,
  },

  {
    question:
      " David Beckham became president of which newly founded club in 2018?",
    option1: "Bergamo Calcio",
    option2: "Inter Miami",
    option3: "West London Blue",
    option4: "The Potteries",
    ans: 2,
  },

  {
    question:
      " In 2011, a 5th tier match in Argentina saw a record number of red cards. How many were given out?",
    option1: "6",
    option2: "11",
    option3: "22",
    option4: "36",
    ans: 4,
  },
];
